Finding aid for the DES Action, Connecticut records SSC.MS.00791
Sophia Smith Collection
- 2017 transfer of records, 1978-1998; 2017-S-0043; 3.75 Linear Feet (3 record center cartons)
  - Medical journal articles, 1951-1994 (Box 3)
  - "Unlikely references to DES" (in Silence of the Lambs), 1988 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1985 (Box 3)
  - NIH information, 1980-1993 (Box 3)
  - Other Advocacy Groups, 1978-1992 (Box 3)
  - History of DES outline (Box 3)
  - Personal Testimonies, 1979-1993 (Box 3)
  - Toxic Tort Litigation (Box 3)
  - Caren Glickson diary: DES Sequence, 1994 (Box 3)
  - "Friends of Caren Glickson" Appeal letter, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Caren Glickson, personal correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 3)
  - Caren Glickson, political correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - Caren Glickson, speeches/notes, 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Local newspaper coverage, 1980-1992 (Box 3)
  - Newspaper articles re: Caren Glickson, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - DES CT, forms and handouts, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Paula Montes files, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, handouts, and brochures, 1981-1991 (Box 3)
  - Physician evaluation form (Box 3)
  - DES Action New Jersey and Canada newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Caren Glickson, 15th Reunion (Wellesley) statement, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Coalition for Consumer Justice, 1986 (Box 3)
  - "DES—Were You Exposed?" Script for Slide Show (with slides), 1979 (Box 3)
  - Button templates and buttons (Box 3)
  - "Ask Your Mother" educational recording, approximately 1980-1992; 2 Cassettes (2 copies of the same recording) (Box 3)
    Audiocassettes; Esposito, Sally J.; Glickson, Caren E.; Hyman, Debra
  - Talk of the Town," Sally Esposito radio interview, 1992; 1 Cassettes (Box 3)
  - DES Action radio spots, approximately 1980-1992; 2 Reels (Box 3)
    Audiotapes; Esposito, Sally J.; Glickson, Caren E.; Hyman, Debra
  - Alice Eve Cohen, Solo performance artist—"Jessica's Cervix," "Elegy," "The Play That Knows What you Want," and "The Infinite Voyage", 1990; 2 items (2 copies of the same VHS videotape ) (Box 3)
    Videotapes; Esposito, Sally J.; Glickson, Caren E.; Hyman, Debra